bro I got nothing to say I got nothing
to talk about all I do everyday is just
like cook eggs and make beats like my
rat about I'd make a crispy egg so what
you do is you heat up a stainless steel
pan till it's like almost smoking when
you put the olive oil in you drop a
little bit of olive oil in drop two eggs
right into that they're gonna explode a
little bit they're gonna get crazy
they're gonna bubble it's okay okay
you just let the egg do its thing it'll
form a crisp around the edges dried
oregano sea salt crushed black pepper
peperoncino
I cook eggs for real you can't you can't
you can't be talking about food and I
didn't even eat the tree yeah
[Music]
how did me and Kimmy beets link up well
really what happened was um I was on the
tableau tour at the time and Mark was
like you know I want to get you in a
booth for kidney beats and stuff like
that so we ended up just linking up is
just making stuff so we yeah we had made
probably like two or three or four songs
over the course of like four or five
sessions the first year that we met and
nothing really stood out that crazy and
then we ended up having a beef over a
record a beat got used for something
else
it was opposed to be on Zoo Denzel hated
me for nine months it was a very very
like six or seven months but I hated
this man for a long time it was like uh
anti can beat anything that had
something to do with him I didn't what I
did not want to hear this [__] no I know
I don't like playing names
look I ain't no I don't do that [__] and
then the cave started and when Freddy
did the cave his cousin had showed him
that and he hit me up like [__] kind of
hard like we did the cave episode we
started unlocked that day yeah yeah the
cave was the first time that mean Denzel
had seen each other since we had had
like a real altercation about a song and
we had spoken on the phone a little bit
tried to like crush things as men and
just get down to making some music
together again but he came there that
day and when we had finished the episode
these are just episodes like the cave
isn't really about the song
it's about the banter and about the
people on the show so when we had
finished that song the song came out
super hard we actually heard it today
and I was like this sounds great okay
yeah the Freestyle two season finale I
was inside it was one of the only
episodes that felt like a real song or
like a real moment and so that day he
stuck around in the first song we made
after that is the first real song here
on the project but you know that had to
happen you know I don't think this
project would be this project we hadn't
had the relationship we had had
everything been perfect and cool and I
had one song on Zoo and this and that
there would probably be no reason for us
to get in and make unlocked you know so
everything happens for a reason because
after I called him squashed everything I
was over it I said long as this is one
thing I don't want beats you already
made
I want beats from scratch and we're
gonna be in a studio together and he was
like for sure that was it that's how we
did it here I've gotten myself in
trouble before by preaching how
important it is to be with the artist
because some kids make it like they feel
like you're saying if you're not in the
room with a rapper you're not a real
producer did it up that's not the truth
there's great records that get made over
the internet over the phone all the time
but when you are in the room with
someone especially someone like Denzel
and every crazy idea or a weird thing
they might say you can take into account
and include that in what you're making
and whenever you're recording the vocals
or whenever they're making the song
happen you can be there to say oh whoa
he wanted to feel like this let me make
this left turn here where I would have
made a right turn that's the what you
don't get whenever you're just setting
beats in an email
yeah projects can't feel as cohesive is
this whenever it's all talked about on
the phone here in man the only thing we
really talked on the forum about it
wasn't about the music music was already
made it was just the planning the plan
like how we gonna execute this plan and
you know he didn't know how serious I
could get when it comes down to
executing something so when he's seen it
firsthand were unlocked and everything
dang he got a glimpse like oh [__]
whatever you saying he actually was
about doing you know yeah a lot of
artists say things in the studio about
want the video to be this I want the
merch to be this we gonna do this
premiere and all this kind of stuff and
nothing ends up happening it's not
always their fault it might be their
team might be the label it could be
anything but everything we spoke about
in that three day period happened you
know we did a secret show in New York we
did a film premiere we put out of movie
basically is 20 minutes long it's like
these were all the things he was saying
to me and I was like yeah okay cool see
what you see it it really came to
fruition we had this thing set up as
soon as we finished the project
boom got a mix got a mastered and that
was it got a cover done that was it we
was ready to go now it was talking about
like what we're gonna do with videos and
knowing that how we made it we didn't
want no singles there's no singles like
the project is the single you know so we
ended up just taking that and running
with it and make it know like pretty
much like a 23 short film 23 minute
short film which will probably be an
episode that you see on TV without
commercials but we had to figure out a
way to get people to tune in to
something long form no snippet or
perfect artwork or whatever that me and
Denzel drop is gonna get that much hype
and that's where all the beef [__] came
into play you came into my life started
yelling at me on Twitter you tweeted how
you don't [__] producers all this type
of [__] those tweets those moments
eighteen thousand retweets in two
seconds 20,000 likes in two seconds when
you post your artwork gets this many
likes whenever you start beefing it gets
this many like so we took a little book
out a couple people pages and just tried
to hype it up that way and see if it
impacted anybody and it did and it did
and literally that whole morning was
Olin complex and all these big people
posting about this beef between me and
Denzel and blah blah blah and it's like
we tricked y'all everybody watched the
movie and everybody was all up in arms
but the only kids were really up in arms
about it were the kids who ten minutes
ago we're like oh they must have beat
each other's ass so then they found out
it was faking they got trained it was
like well what the [__] so it's just
like every rapper dad I know when they
hate another rapper or whoever the case
may be is like it's like high school
[__] y'all talking [__] but you ain't
gonna do [__] you know I'm saying like I
took that and I was like okay I'm gonna
talk [__] but we don't make money for
talking [__] but I really wanted to do
something like guerilla style you know
like you ever watch the gorillas music
music videos I wanted to do something
like that for diet but like each track
based on how it sounds was based off
like something that came from my
childhood but if you hear cosmic it
sounds like you're gonna war is like a
fight track that you hear in a moon
so cowboy bebop was like the base of
that quintero Watanabe that's one of my
favorite directors you know so I've used
that as inspiration for that and samurai
Champloo uh when it came down to just
you know track 2 which was take it back
we had to use that who's lucky cuz it's
in your face and his dark is gritty
and start saying it creeps in so we use
something from the geunji world which
who created um
Musa Maki and just made that what it was
but these were like conversations
throughout the music process where he
would say this feels like this imagine
if this song goes to here and then we're
gonna be in this world we gonna look
like Robot Chicken and done all these
different things like he had this whole
plan set up of the visuals when I'm only
ever thinking about the music you know I
mean that's even beyond me he would say
all this stuff and I Blake yeah cool and
they would send me drawings and I'd be
like does that me like yeah cool and
then all of a sudden we're on the film
set we're doing voiceovers we got these
outfits that are designed by him we have
all these things going on he really saw
the whole picture and his team and his
label and myself like just helped him
execute it and that's what the short
film is yeah it's really about the
artistry of me you know I know it's like
that what Kenny - so we both met
somewhere in the middle real artists -
we're gonna do another project we're
gonna do a sequel episode - it's gonna
have animated shorts in there but it's
not gonna be fully animated shorts this
is gonna be different worlds you know
yeah you know I mean when you see a
20-minute episode of your favorite show
you like where the other ten episodes
type [__] like when you listen to a
whole album you like cool see the next
album in a year this didn't feel like an
album so doing another one doesn't feel
like a follow-up or a sequel or whatever
it's just like we on Episode two exactly
now we're gonna quiz each other and find
out who really knows who okay let me let
me start
what's my full name Kenneth Blum the
third my middle name is Charles but
we're gonna let that slide all right
what's my full name
this is the easiest [__] question
Denzel Curie oh my god when is my
birthday May how do you even know that
yeah you're Taurus brah you're amazed
something was it baby 10 is 10
that's crazy he really knows my work
when is my birthday December 25th god of
his rap [__]
no [__] that's hard 16 oh yeah I was my
second guess what city was not born in
Connecticut how do you know me so well
oh that's a state but yeah I was born in
Connecticut what city massachusett
that's another state that's another
state I was born in Greenwich
Connecticut I don't like to talk about
it what city was not born in Carroll
City okay let's go name as many of my
projects as you can
seven seven seven anger management
[Music]
Netflix and deal can I say loudly okay
say no that's not a project Oh guys they
unlock them okay yeah okay a lot you
already gonna beat me what's the friend
get what's the Freddie Gibbs Freddie
wait yeah name as many of my projects as
you can do I think I know about all song
names got hours blood in blood out
that's technically not a project what do
you care came out for a lot as a mix as
a big I didn't count as the project was
some kind with the word
Beltran's my project now it doesn't mean
this is a person it's just me most
what's the wouldn't have liked nostalgia
and the neighbors are nostalgic 60 from
this town 64 mmm what was the early one
that Dan was talking about
unlock lock okay
cuz I'm not part two is coming so Rome
account oh you leave it this one don't
find you what's my favorite strain are
you like a hybrid
yeah I do my favourite strain is
probably right now bisque off it's a
little bit of a bit Scotty mixed with a
little bit of something else it's fire
what's not for restraining sobriety
what's my favorite cereal okay [__] I
don't know that you got it like a Lucky
Charms vibe you know like a cat meat you
say my my friend review your personality
makes me feel like peanut butter Cap'n
Crunch I'm more of a recent cereal guy
yes
can't get that one I'm taking that one
okay okay you look like a frosted flakes
an exit close but no he is a Kellogg's
cereal I think so yes hello is Kellogg's
Froot Loops no I think healthier raisin
bran I like the Special K Liat damn do
you ever had the Special K with the
chocolate it it is so crazy cuz it's in
the part of the aisle where you're like
I'm not [__] with anything over here
but I'll tell you thank you shut out
Kellogg what's my favorite snack chips
yeah you don't know how do you know all
this [__] we mean I don't know man you
probably like right you look like one of
them song vinegar as [__] maybe
Pringles
I'll put a sour cream and onion Pringle
will get me yeah well it wasn't I wasn't
everybody's neck bro your [__] like like
ear one acai bowl and you got that right
oh actually is my first guys who's my
favorite rapper yeah I don't know man is
it yeah is that easy
okie yeah he's a very roundabout there
rapper who's my favorite rapper you
should know this he's one half of a duo
of us one half of a duo think of the
best duo of all time Andre let's go
what's my favorite cartoon let's see for
you this is hard oh my man can I put can
I say cowboy bebop that's one of them
you can't casually talk about anime with
him he's going into real fast I forgot
so Kimmy beats you watch cartoon not
like that
I know you don't I do have a favorite
though I'm just gonna take a shot in the
dark here you go say some deep cut and
make sure that no nose I got
Bojack horseman no okay that's the vibe
I give you yeah no official favorite cuz
this is the only question I got wrong my
favorite cartoon right now I'll be like
big mouth I think big mouth was funny
and that [__] is funny as [__]
when I was growing up Dragon Ball Z oh
really oh damn
yeah but you can't stop me no you can't
say Dragon Ball Z to him because he'll
start sunning you because that's like
entry-level animation so he'll start
getting so mad
yeah Dragon Ball Z everybody loves that
I grew up on that that's the entry but
Cowboy Bebop
as what it is that's my [__] yo this is
Denzel curry and this is Kenny beets
shame on luck right now we're the
unofficial official duo shut off top
legs obviously knew more about a blanket
on projects that's not you know we're
true friend [__]